sermons4kids.com 2006-05-07

# Children's Sermons for Sermon 4 Kids | Object Lessons & Children's Sermons

| 

## Sermons4Kids Privacy Policy   
  
---  
  
Greetings from Sermons4Kids and welcome to our site! We provide the following information to assure you that we are concerned about and respect your privacy while visiting our Web site. Sermons4Kids will never sell, lease or rent your confidential information. We will always endeavor to take steps to assure that any information you provide to us will remain secure. Please take a moment to review the following valuable information. 

Collection of Information 

Sermons4Kids does not collect personal information without your knowledge while you are visiting our Web site. Sermons4Kids does, however, allow you to provide personal information on our Web site. The type of information we collect directly corresponds with the service you request. For example, you can ask us a question or make a suggestion on ways which we could make our ministry more effective. The information we collect is only the information needed to respond to your specific question or suggestion. We cannot respond to a question if you do not include your email address.

If you make a donation, Sermons4Kids will collect the information necessary to complete this transaction. This information is collected to provide you with a receipt for your records and to provide information for records and reports which may be required by the IRS. We do not have access to credit card information on donations made through PayPal.

Use of Information 

Sermons4Kids uses the information provided by you to: 

  * Respond to your correspondence, questions, comments, or suggestions. 
  * Contact you via email to confirm specific information requests.
  * Confirm subscription information.

Sermons4Kids does not sell, rent or lease your confidential information to others. We will disclose confidential information only when required by law. 

Security

All online donations are handled through PayPal. PayPal is secure and is committed to handling your customer information with high standards of information security. Your credit card and information is stored only in encrypted form on computers that are not connected to the Internet. Sermons4Kids does not have access to credit card information given to PayPal. 

Changes to the Privacy Policy 

Sermons4Kids reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time and requests that you review this policy periodically for updates. 

Questions and Suggestion 

Questions or comments regarding this privacy policy may be submitted by mail to Sermons 4 Kids, Inc. 3273 Falcon Drive, Abilene, TX, USA, 79606-3312, or by [**email.**](mailto:webservant@sermons4kids.com)

This Web site may provide links to external Web sites maintained by individuals or organizations external to Sermons4Kids. Once you access information that links you to another Web site, you are subject to the privacy policy of the Web site containing the information you have linked to.
